Subtitle edited by - Aorion -
"The Gallows (2015)" ^ (Run time : 01:20:47)
Beatrice High School
BHS Drama
"The Gallows"
PM 8:47
OCT 29, 1993
Could you make a copy
for us, as well?
I'll have to figure out
how to do this
- when it's all done. I'm just...
- I know.
And Jean was not happy 'cause,
boy, was this thing expensive.
Oh, August.
What shall we do?
Don't worry, Mary.
He wants me.
He's coming for me
and... and no one else.
Do you understand?
August, I'm frightened.
I know, Mary.
Art thou afraid?
Charlie's doing such a good job.
I am no more.
Yeah, I'm really surprised
considering the last-minute
change, but it looks good.
August... kiss me.
No, please don't.
Please don't do it, August.
Please.
Do you... do you know
what they're doing
for the spring play,
by any chance?
No, I have no idea.
Um...
They did a great job
on the gallows.
For crimes against
the township of bedford...
Including robbery...
Perjury...
Adultery...
And fraternizing with a noble...
I hereby sentence you...
August Benjamin rutherford...
To death...
By hanging
on this 29th day...
- Oh
- ohh.
Charlie?! Charlie?!
Charlie!! Charlie!!
Oh, my...
Oh, my god!
Grab the rope!
Grab him!
Get a doctor!
He's not breathing!
Lights up.
All right.
Let's nail this, guys.
Yeah.
Let's nail this,
Mr. schwendiman.
You got it.
Oh, August, you came.
Oh.
Don't worry, my love.
They're...
He's coming for...
He wants me.
Project nice
and loud to the back, please.
- Come on, Reese.
- He wants me.
He's coming for me.
Is she gonna throw up?
Dost...
Dost thou understand?
Thou...
Thou shall be safe here?
Oh, August...
For I am frightened.
Art thou?
Dig deep.
Find those tears.
Not anymore.
Oh, what?
Dude.
August...
Just give me one last kiss.
Is he gonna do it this time?
Here it is, bro.
Pucker up for that theater nerd.
- Yeah.
- Cut.
Oh.
Ohh!
- Reese.
- Yeah?
Nice job, dude.
- Pfeifer, great job.
- Thank you.
Everyone else, that was good.
God, she's obnoxious.
A little more work
on the lines, Reese.
Yeah, you need to work on 'em.
You need a little bit
more work on them...
Before tomorrow night.
Oh.
- Yeah, take a moment right now...
- The play is tomorrow.
And just go over
those pages again.
Wow.
Jesus.
Oh, Reese,
you're breakin' my poor heart!
Oh, this is good.
For those of you
watching along at home,
that is why football players
do not do drama.
Ryan.
You're supposed to stay
in the booth.
No.
Hey, Reese.
Can I borrow your blouse?
Why, man?
I need some clarity, bro.
Help me out here.
Isn't this embarrassing, dude?
Like, you're chokin'
worse than Charlie did.
Dude, they're gonna
tear you apart in here.
Don't do it!
Oh my...
Don't bring the camera
in the locker room.
This is more booby
than the girl locker room.
Dude, this isn't the girl's.
Who brings a camera
into the men's locker room?
Oh, my god.
Get that shit outta here.
That's disgusting.
No one wants to see that.
- My boy's gonna be a superstar!
- Yes!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Look at those tights, Peter Pan!
Yo, are you serious?
Why can't you just stay
up in the booth?
I was in the booth, dude.
The booth camera sucks.
That's why I have my camera.
Besides, I have practice.
Come on.
You coulda done shop.
You coulda done home ec.
You're wearing knickers, bro!
Come on.
Reese.
Knickers, dude!
Stop walking.
I'll find you, Reese.
Hey, big shot.
Get suited up. Let's go.
There's Miss. Shannon.
Do you still have a husband,
Miss. Shannon?
- Goodbye.
- Love you, too.
And another one up!
Cassidy!
- Out.
- Ryan! Come on.
Cassidy!
What're you doin'?
I told you not to mess with this!
It's not a toy.
- Pssh.
- Don't "pssh" me!
So, what's it like
being a drama techie?
- Such a bitch. Are you kidding?
- Whoa!
What? If I had known
there was a drama requirement...
I love it.
I mean, I get to hang out with
the most unattractive girls.
I'm late to practice every day.
- Hey, Ryan, how's drama?
- Oh, how's drama?
Yeah, how's it hanging out with all
your new little drama buddies?
At least I'm not around you,
squirt.
Are you trying to defend
your little drama buddies?
Yeah, well, your mom.
- Hey. Hey, big shot!
- Yes, coach!
- Practice? Hello?
- Yeah, Ryan.
Let's go, big shot!
Hey, there they are!
There's some of your buddies
right there.
They're not my buddies.
Take this.
Take this thing, man.
- Watch this.
- Oh, my god. Oh, no.
It's up!
- Ohh!
- Woo!
Go get the trainer!
- Nailed it!
- Vicious.
Right in the schnoz, dude.
Yo, David, how ya doing?
Hey, what's happenin'?
- Working late tonight?
- You know it.
- Time for a vacation, huh?
- You guessed that, too.
And here's the 1993 cast.
Just as geeky as now.
And there he is.
Charlie grimille.
Unbelievably morbid that they still
have a picture of him up here.
Don't forget your costume.
Chris, turn off
the cell phones, please.
In the drama room
as well as the theater.
That's the rule.
Turn them off or be suspended!
No cell phone, okay?
No cell phones.
All right. Now listen up.
Eyes forward, everyone.
Tomorrow night is the show.
It's been a long process.
Not always easy, right, Pfeifer?
- Mm-Mm.
Especially not
with the school board,
but we got through that.
But, um, I think
we're gonna do okay.
Pfeifer, you had a couple of words
you wanted to say. Go ahead.
Of course
she has something to say.
Thank you, guys.
First off, I would like you guys
to take a peek at the programs.
They're done, and they are
identical to the 1993 ones.
- Oh, my god. Thank god.
- So thank you, Brittany.
Thank you guys so much
for helping me
make this show possible.
We've worked so hard.
We've had such a great time.
I feel so proud to be
a part of the gallows.
I just can't wait
to see it finally finished.
Me neither.
C'est fini!
So thank you guys.
Thank you, Pfeifer.
Our assistant director,
Pfeifer Ross, everyone.
And what do we say?
- Break a leg.
- Break a leg, Reese.
Thank you, guys. Let's go.
Backstage.
- Shoos! Mr. BHS.
- What's up, my man?
- Oh, look at this.
- What are you doing in here?
- My two favorite characters.
- Peasant number five, hangman.
You guys even have lines?
- I think I clap or something.
- There you go.
If coach could see you guys now,
you'd be kicked off in a second.
Yeah, get that camera
outta here, man.
It's a mandatory class, man.
Thanks for bringing this stuff.
It's like Halloween down here.
- Yeah, most definitely.
- Yeah, party cen...
Oh, ho.
What do we have here?
What is this thing?
- That's the old hangman costume.
- Looks pretty dumb.
Some kid told us
not to touch it.
Did a little drama nerd
tell you not to touch it?
I think he told me, too.
But then I didn't listen to him
'cause I'm such a badass.
Dan and mark,
can I see you guys up on stage?
- Oh, damn it.
- Ryan!
- Yeah?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
I know that you don't take
any of this seriously, okay?
I don't.
I'm sorry.
No, I will.
Okay. It's important
to a lot of people.
So show a little respect
in the theater, okay?
- All right.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Yeah, right.
Look at him in those khakis.
What a joke.
- I'm fine.
- What are you doin'?
I don't know. Just trying
to get through this thing.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Oh, I'm Charlie.
I'm dead.
Oh.
Oh, I got a trick for you guys.
Watch.
Watch this.
Ready?
How creepy is that?
God.
Yo, yo, yo.
Dude.
Smile for the camera, man.
Oh, come on.
Look, I'm sorry about
hitting you with the football.
You were wide open.
Come on.
Can I at least
help you with this stuff?
No!
And don't touch the fly rigs.
They're dangerous.
Wow.
Okay, stage boy.
August is not
who he seems he is, Mary.
To the audience, John.
Can't you see?
He is pretending to be a noble
that he might win your love.
He should turn himself in.
He must be hanged!
August will not turn himself in!
He loves me!
But, sir, the hangman
will take Mary in his place.
His sentence is death.
Nerd.
What shall I do?
What shall I do, father?
Reese, come on.
- Now, Reese.
- What shall I do, father?
Reese!
- There he is.
- Good timing, Reese.
- Don't come out with the book.
- What shall I-"What shall I do?"
And then you come in.
The parents of the nerds.
There they are.
And look at these guys.
Contain your excitement,
gentlemen.
I don't even know
if this lady's a parent.
She's here literally every day.
Sits in the same spot.
- Wait, so you were in the old show?
- The original show.
- Like the original?
- Yep. I was there.
What was that like?
I don't know if you ever recover
from something like this.
It was...
horrifying.
The students were upset.
The teachers were upset.
- Charlie had a girlfriend.
- He had a girlfriend?
Oh, I didn't really know her,
but she was devastated.
I've been here when my kids have
been here, and things have happened.
Lights have gone on when there was
no one in the lighting booth.
Doors have been opened
and shut and locked.
There's all kinds of stories
around here. Um-Hum.
Oh, no, no, no.
They're Patty-caking!
He's slapping hands
with another dude.
And zero hot girls.
Ew.
Whoa. And the queen.
Not in a million years.
I hate this class.
Hollywood!
- What's up, brother?
- Hey.
What are you doing?
Practicing?
- Mm-hmm.
- Is it working?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
It makes no sense, dude.
I mean, this is torture.
Why don't you just
call out sick? You know?
- Put an end to this.
- I can't call out sick.
I call out sick two to three
times a week, minimum.
Just do it.
I have a responsibility
to these people.
I'm the lead in the play.
To what people?
What are you talking about?
A responsibility to these guys?
Come on.
You're just go...
Give me this.
* LOOK AT ME !
♥ ♥
Holy shit.
Reese?
Do you like Pfeifer?
- No, Ryan. No.
- You do!
Don't you?
You like Pfeifer!
Ryan, seriously, no, I don't.
That's why you're doing this?
- Oh, my god. Does she know?
- Ryan.
- She doesn't know.  She doesn't.
- I don't... Ryan.
- Reese, your boy's got this, dude.
- Stop it, Ryan.
- Just talk to schwendiman.
I got this one, man. Ha ha.
Hey, drama queen!
Hey, hey, hey!
Pfeifer!
- Hey, Ryan!
- Wait a second.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on.
I need to talk to you about
Reese.
What about Reese?
He has
a big-ass crush on you.
Like, he wants to be on you.
Pfeifer, please.
Talk to me about Reese.
- Yes.
- What's going on there?
Uh. Reese is gonna do great.
I have complete faith in him.
He knows his lines.
He's gonna be fine.
Are you kidding me?
Everybody knows he's gonna choke
like Charlie did.
We don't say that name, Ryan.
I've told you that.
- It's bad luck.
- I'm sorry.
I don't get you drama nerds
and your jargon.
It's like, "good luck"
is bad luck.
Breaking a leg is supposed to be
a good thing?
- Exactly!
- And "c'est fini"?
What the hell is that?
Oh, my god.
Pfeifer, back to the point.
After the show bombs,
how is it gonna affect
you and Reese?
The show isn't going to bomb,
Ryan, okay?
We're gonna finish the show.
It's gonna look great!
C'est fini!
C'est fi-what?
You're from Nebraska.
- Ryan!
- What?
Price needs you.
Who's price?
The stage manager.
The stage man...
Oh.
Stage boy.
Yeah.
Hey there, chief.
How you doin', bud?
What can I help you with?
It's number 28 here.
It's just a little too heavy
for me, you know.
You can do it.
I probably can.
Yes.
You just can't...
It's pretty stuck.
Is it this one?
Price got some balls, dude.
You just need it pulled down?
It's fine if you can't do it.
- Are you sure it's this one?
- It's this one.
It's fine if you can't do it.
I can do it.
It just needs a good pull.
- Ohh!
- Oh!
That's-
That's gonna leave a mark.
- Smile for the camera!
- Oh, man.
Come here, you sick...
Hey!
Stage boy.
- Come here, boy!
- No, no, look!
You're done.
Look, it was just a joke!
We're even! We're even!
- It was a joke?! It was not funny!
- Please don't hurt me!
- It was not a funny joke!
- Okay.
- What?!
- Stop, Ryan!
Come on, price.
- Come on. Ryan.
- You're lucky, boy.
- Ryan, stop.
- We're even.
No.
This isn't over.
Price.
You okay?
Yeah.
What?
No way.
Hey, hey, Brooke.
It's Kelly.
Okay.
What is up with this door?
It's broken.
Everybody knows that.
No.
What?
Reese!
Dude.
Dude, Reese.
My man.
Oh!
- What?
- Do you still wanna do this play?
Do you still wanna do this play?
Are you kidding me?
Okay. Listen.
I was talking to Pfeifer
and that stupid stage boy,
and I was chasing him,
but I found this door.
I found a door over here
that's unlocked.
It never locks.
Always open.
What are you guys talking about?
What'd she say?
Who?
Pfeifer.
Oh, my god, Reese.
You like Pfeifer?
Oh. Reese.
This is your chance.
We break into the school
tonight.
We come in through that door.
We ruin the set.
10 minutes. You don't have to
do the play anymore.
That's awesome.
Cassidy, please.
What do you think, Reese?
You're insane, man.
Reese, it's a great plan.
- No!
- Why not?
No! Ryan, this is illegal.
Put the camera down.
Why would you even
want to film this?
Bail on the show.
If I bail on this show,
they all hate me.
Esp...
Especially Pfeifer.
And if you don't bail
on the show,
you let everyone down
and they all hate you.
Especially Pfeifer.
Dude, I'm done.
I'm done sugarcoating
this whole thing.
You suck.
You're a terrible actor,
and you need to do
something about it.
Why not do something
that's not your fault?
Tear this mother down.
Look, they're gonna come in
tomorrow.
They're gonna be like,
"Oh, my god! The set's broken.
What are we gonna do?"
And who's there for Pfeifer
to lean on in her time of need?
Dude, you are!
It's a win!
- I'm a freakin' genius!
- You're not a genius.
What time?
You're not coming, Cassidy.
Yes, I'm coming.
No, you're not.
You're a cheerleader.
What the hell does that
have to do with anything?
You didn't let me finish.
You're a cheerleader that likes
to do other girl dance stuff,
not cool, awesome, scary stuff
at the school at night.
I'll pick you up at 9:00.
Okay. Dude.
Are you in?
Do you have tools?
Yes, Reese!
Yeah.
Yeah, I got tools.
God, Reese. I can't believe
you like Pfeifer.
Shut up!
Why did you tell her?
Boo!
All right.
Between you and me...
- Ryan?
- Mom! What are you doing?
- Oh, I'm sorry. Sorry.
- What are you...
What are you doing, mom?
I told you that
I just needed 5 minutes.
All right, baby.
Stay in here.
In and out, babe.
Please.
That's what she said.
Trick or treat, Housers.
- This play is...
- Why is it so important to you?
You know, you don't understand.
I don't want you
doing this play.
Why do you care?
I just don't wanna do football.
You should've stayed
on the football team.
- Okay. Well, I'm not...
You finish things that you start.
You don't walk away.
- Yo. Yo, Reese.
- Like a flake.
All right, well, I gotta go.
- Damn, man.
- What?
- Rick Houser.
- Evening, Ryan.
How ya doin'?
Dandy.
What's this?
A camera.
For the play.
- Play, huh?
- Yep.
School night,
all right, buddy?
Yeah, I know. We're just going
over to Ryan's for a little.
Don't worry, Mr. Houser.
We'll have him back by bedtime.
- What's up.
- Hi, Reese.
- Yeah.
- Back seat, babe.
You got it.
Reese.
Your dad's got a point, man.
He doesn't have one.
I'm not my dad, Ryan.
I know.
That would be impossible.
But you didn't need
to quit the team.
Well, I quit the team.
And I'm not gettin' back
on the team.
Okay.
Can we talk for...
- It's like watching an infant
roll around on the stage.
- Babe, two seconds.
- Gosh, you're just a wonderful best friend.
- Reese, please.
Okay, excuse me. Reese,
can you please explain to us
what it is about Pfeifer,
'cause I don't see it.
I don't get it. I'm pretty sure you don't.
Right, babe?
Here is him on sta...
Pf-Pf-Pf-Pfeifer.
C-c-can I k-k-kiss you?
You almost kissed
a real girl once, right?
Come on!
Yes, I've kissed her.
- I think I remember.
- Who?
- I've kissed plenty of girls.
She's really... she's a
she's a nice person.
- She really is.
- "A nice person"?
Just sit down and talk to her
for like 5 minutes.
All right, all right, all right.
- Here we go.
- Dude, I'm so stoked.
I cannot believe
you talked me into this.
No one's gonna believe
that we did this.
Can I get a "for Pfeifer"
on three.
1, 2, 3.
For Pfeifer!
- You're a...
- I'm not joining in on that.
You're sure it's fine
to park the car there?
Yeah, dude.
It's completely fine.
So relax.
Can I get some stealth, please?
- Fuck.
- Jesus!
- Sorry.
- Get up, babe! Babe, get up!
- This is so stupid. This is stupid.
- My boy, Reese Houser.
- Just lower your voice just a little bit.
- Tradin' in his baby balls
for some big ol' man testes.
Moment of truth.
Do the honors.
Do it, dude.
Come on.
Okay.
It opened.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
It's open.
Where's the light switch?
Can we find some lights?
- Shit!
- Whoa.
- Find a light switch.
- Yeah.
The lights aren't working?
What, is the power out
or something?
I cannot see anything remotely.
Just ask
and you shall receive, man.
Yes.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
Slow down.
There's somethin'
I wanna do first.
We're here to take down the set.
Let's take it down so we can...
I know, dude. All right?
Let's just...
Come on, please.
This place is pretty different
at night, huh?
Ryan, can we just get this done?
Yes!
Oh, ho, ho.
Score!
Stage boy, man,
I told you not to mess with me.
But you did.
And now, I got some good stuff
up my sleeve.
I have a couple options
of what I would like you to wear
at tomorrow night's play.
Here's option number one.
You know?
Little booby holes in there.
Number two,
which is my personal favorite.
I hope you enjoy it as well.
Ryan, stop messin' around.
Are you finished?
Yeah.
Okay.
There's your sign, Cassidy.
Shh.
Yeah, this place
is super creepy at night.
What do you think, man?
Let's just take this thing down
and get outta here.
Copy that.
Charlie.
Come out and play.
What?!
Cassidy,
what the hell are you doing?
What I thought
we came here to do.
That's my girl!
All right.
I wanna get somethin'.
Yeah.
Felt good.
Lemme get another one.
- Get this one?
- Will you...
Want me to get this one?
- What's up? Huh?
- Attaboy!
What is up?!
You gotta like it.
Bring that light over here,
please.
Will you keep it lit?
Don't strip it, man.
Who gives a shit?
Are you gonna help me?
- One down, bro.
- Will you take something apart, too?
I'm holdin' the light.
I know, but I'd like you
to take something apart.
- That way, I'm not doing this by myself.
- Okay.
"Help me take it apart." Whatever.
The guy with no screwdriver.
Okay.
For you, sir.
Let's go, Shakespeare.
Come on, my man.
Let's hear some lines.
What?
Now or never.
Let's hear some lines.
What are you doing?
Get up here
and help me take this apart.
It was your idea.
August.
August?
- I'm so frightened.
- Just do it.
August, speak!
Please!
Don't worry, Mary. He wants me.
He's coming for me.
Oh, my god.
What are you doing?!
I'm doing the line.
Just say the...
Just say 'em better.
He wants me.
He is coming for me.
No one else.
Dost thou understand?
Thou shall be safe...
Whoa!
Get down here!
Shit, cut the light!
Lose the tools, dude!
Lose the tools.
- Did you see anyone?
- No, I didn't see anybody.
- No, but I heard them over there!
- Is it that janitor? David?
- Who?
- Who else would be in here?
What do we do?
Reese, do you see anything?
Reese!
Okay, let's go out the back.
- Now?
- Yes, right now.
Let's go.
- Oh, my god!
- Oh, shit.
Pfeifer?!
You're kidding me!
- Oh, my god.
- Pfeifer.
This is gonna be really good.
Reese?
Oh, my gosh.
What are you guys doing here?
- What-What are you doing here?
- Yeah.
I saw Reese's car. Reese, I saw
your car in the parking lot.
I told you that we should've
parked somewhere else, dude.
- Yeah, no kidding.
- Can I please talk to you?
Yeah, yeah. Let's just talk
over here for a second.
- Ryan, let's go.
- Alone, please.
- Ryan.
- Fine. Fine!
Reese.
- What should I say?
- I don't know.
- Make something up.
- Ryan.
I'm just gonna leave the light
right here for you guys.
Reese, so what's going on?
What are you guys doing here?
Uh...
Well, we...
Eh. What-What if you guys
would've gotten caught?
What if it wasn't me that caught you?
You would have got in some...
You wouldn't have been
able to do the show.
I know, I know.
It's...
It's stupid.
I don't know what I was...
What we were thinking.
Hey, listen.
I'm sorry.
What are you guys doing here?
Uh...
You know, to...
- I was...
- What?
I... We came to-
to practice a little bit.
You know, to go over some
of the lines and stuff
because tomorrow's the show
and I don't...
Feel confident.
I don't...
I don't wanna let you down.
Pfeifer.
I really don't.
Okay.
Promise?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Okay? Okay.
Let's get outta here.
We shouldn't be here.
Let's go.
Oh, my god. Oh my god.
What are we gonna do?
Oh, it's so dark.
Night vision app.
I know. I know.
Hit a little snag there
with drama queen coming in
and ruining the whole thing.
But...
smooth McReese
is gonna walk us outta this
so we can we finish this up.
Cassidy!
What are you doing?
Fixing the set, babe.
I mean, we just took the set down!
What are you doing?
Yeah, but Pfeifer's here.
She knows.
She doesn't know.
Look.
Reese is out there
comin' up with some lame story.
Pfeifer's gonna leave.
This thing is practically
taken apart.
- Reese will just call us when he's done.
- Okay, no.
- And we can finish the job.
- 'Cause Pfeifer's here and she knows.
And look, I don't even have
any service on my cell phone.
All right.
That's weird,
but what do you expect
when you're on it 24/7?
- Hey, Ryan. Stop being dumb.
- I'm not being dumb.
If you wanna leave, go outside,
call Chelsea,
have her come get you.
And you can leave.
But I'm staying.
God.
This is so stupid.
It's not stupid, Ryan.
It's over. She knows.
It's not stupid.
You're stupid.
I told you
this was gonna happen.
- I'm not stupid.
- Yeah, but did I not say,
"Cassidy, if you decide to come,
do not back out
because you get scared or... "
- I'm not backing out.
- You're clearly backing out!
Lookit!
Where am I going right now?
Right to the door...
What the hell?
Funny. Okay?
This thing
isn't supposed to lock.
- Ryan.
- What?!
- Just open the frickin' door.
- Oh, just open the... okay.
Lemme give it another shot.
I can't unlock it.
- Pfeifer. Gimme that.
- Excuse me.
I can't unlock it.
- Pfeifer. Gimme that.
- Excuse me.
Is there some kind of trick
to this door, Pfeifer?
No. There's not a trick.
Why isn't it opening?
- I don't know.
- You kidding me?
- Ryan, what'd you do?
- He doesn't have service either.
- I don't have service.
- Ryan, he doesn't have it.
Guys, we shouldn't be
in this situation, okay?
- Just find another door.
- What happened to this door?
I have no idea.
How does that not work?
We gotta go try something else.
That should open this door.
They're barred.
What about the windows
in the classroom?
The classes are locked.
Cassidy, someone's locked
these doors, all right. Okay.
- This doesn't make any sense, dude.
- You guys are gonna get
in trouble. Not me.
Ryan, let's go.
- Cassidy, we're trying to go.
- Let's just get out, okay?!
Yeah, I wanna get out of here.
Thank you, Pfeifer.
- Do you, Ryan?
- Yes, I wanna go.
You still wanna finish the job?
- You wanna finish it?
- Cassidy.
- Finish what job?
- What do you think about it now?
- Do not do that.
- Do not what? I don't care anymore.
- Shut your mouth.
We came to break up the set,
Pfeifer.
- We came to break up the set.
- Are you kidding me?
-Reese, Ryan, and I all came here to
break up the set.
- Are you serious?
- What do you want me to do? What?
- What is your problem?
I don't have a problem.
I wanna get the hell out.
Cassidy.
- Why would you say that?
- We need to get out!
Pfeifer!
It was my idea, all right?
Pfeifer.
Look, its not what it looks.
- Pfeifer, please.
- Will you listen? Pfeifer!
- Pfeifer, it was my...
- Will you stop talking for a second?
You've done enough.
- This play is an embarrassment!
- Shut up!
You're gonna embarrass everybody!
This needs to stop.
What did you guys do?
What?
I took that noose down.
Reese, I took that down.
You saw me take it down, man.
The stairs?
Can you guys
please stop messing with me?
- This isn't funny.
- We're not messing with you.
What did you guys do?
Shut up.
- Don't tell me to shut up.
- Stop, Pfeifer.
Practicing?
- You're such a liar.
- I'm sorr...
Reese, what the hell is this?
- Reese!
- I know, I know.
What do we do?
We'll go to the office.
There's a phone there.
We'll call.
- Check this.
- Anything?
- This phone's dead.
- Where's the phone?
- Cassidy, check your cell.
- No, it's not working.
You're kidding me.
Anything that'll help us.
Keys.
I don't know.
Just look.
Have you found it?
Anything?
Go away.
You're making everything worse.
That hurts, man.
I'm sorry.
Hey, did you guys see this?
What?
What is that?
Does it open?
No.
No, come on,
this is not a good idea.
Reese, we have run
into all locked doors.
Lights don't work.
Where are we?
Oh, my gosh.
Shh, shh.
Reese, can you hear that?
What is that?
Shh.
Listen.
Just open it.
Tragedy struck BHS last night
when senior
Charlie grimille died
in what is now being called
a freak accident.
A prop malfunctioned during the
school's presentation of the gallows.
- Charlie.
- Shit.
Charlie.
BHS say his spirit
will live on in the theater.
Should've never ended like this.
It's just not fair.
That's that lady
from the theater.
She was the girlfriend.
Grimille died playing a role
he was never meant to play.
Charlie had originally
been cast as the hangman.
Department and created
a handmade costume.
Charlie was supposed
to be the hangman.
Hey, Charlie.
What happened?
Our leading man. He called in sick.
He called in sick.
Charlie grimille
was the understudy.
What about the hangman, though?
I guess there won't be any.
- Do it.
- Last one.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
What?
Do you see this?
Reese.
Reese, what did you see?
Who was it?
- There's no tape in here.
- What is going on, dude?
- Did you see...
- How do you get it back on?
I don't know.
Help me.
Come on!
- I need to look
- Reese, hold on a sec.
- Come with me.
- Reese, stop!
- Come on.
- Stop, Reese!
Slow down!
I can't see!
Reese, stop!
- Reese! Slow down!
- Slow down!
What?!
Reese, what's going on?
What the hell!
- Take the camera. Take the camera.
- Okay!
Hold it, Cassidy!
Reese, what's wrong?
What are you doing?!
Reese, what?
Talk to us!
What the hell is he doing?
Reese!
Just let me see.
Can I?
What is it?
I don't understand.
Who is that?
Who is...
"AUGUST"
Rick Houser
Reese, is that your dad?
Ryan.
Guys, where's Ryan?
Ryan?
Ryan!
Reese!
Give me the camera back, dude.
Reese.
Guys.
Reese?
Cassidy!
Guys!
Reese!
I don't like this.
Hey, man, you here?
Janitor's still here?
Hello?
David!
What the hell?
Hello?
Shit.
Nah, I'll do it.
What the...
Oh.
What is that?
What...?
Shit.
Cassidy?
Cassidy!
Reese!
Aah!
What the hell?
Is this the wardrobe room?
Reese, where are you?
Aah!
Damn it.
Guys!
What the hell!
God!
- Ryan!
- Ryan?
Guys!
Reese!
- Ryan!
- Ryan?!
- Guys! Reese!
What the hell
is your problem, dude?!
You don't just take the light
and leave me there.
I'm sorry!
I needed the light.
- Tell him
- what happened?!
- What are you doing, man?!
- It was my dad, dude.
- Charlie was supposed to be the hangman.
- I just want to go.
My dad backed out.
That's why Charlie died.
Where the hell were you?!
- Give-Give me the camera!
- Let's get out, Ryan!
What, it was your dad
that backed out?
It's important. The guy that
called in sick was my dad.
- That's why Charlie died.
- That doesn't make any sense.
- Please just listen to me!
All I want to do is
get out of...
Shh.
Cassidy.
Just come over...
Cassidy!
Are you okay?
- Hold on a second, all right? Just hold on.
- I couldn't breathe!
It lifted me
off the freaking ground.
Move out of my way, Pfeifer.
Move! Move. I wanna see it.
Cassidy, I need to get
a good look at it.
- You're not seeing it, Ryan.
- I need to!
- Shh! Just breathe.
- Ryan!
- Don't touch her!
- Get off of me!
- She's my girlfriend.
- Ryan, get me out of here!
- I am done.
- Stop! Let me just see it.
- I am done! Ryan!
- Let me just...
Ryan, you're the reason
we're freaking in here!
- Get the hell out!
- Fine, Cassidy!
And get me out!
- Figure it out yourself!
- You don't give a shit about me!
Let me see.
Reese.
Reese, dude, talk to me.
We need to figure this out.
What is happening?
- I don't know, man.
- What do you mean you don't know?
I mean, what was that
with Cassidy?
The TV?
What was your dad doing there?
- What is that about?
- Stop it.
What do you mean stop it?!
Cassidy's hurt!
And you haven't said anything!
Are you serious?!
Just don't put this on me, man.
You're the reason that
we came here in the first place!
Yeah, I'm the reason we're here,
but maybe you're the reason that
all this shit's happening to us!
- Don't even do that, okay?!
- Why not?!
- Because you brought me here!
- Yeah. I brought you here to help you!
- You were not trying to help me!
- I wanted to help you!
You came here to help yourself.
That is not true!
It was to help you!
And you're the reason
this is going bad!
We're stuck in here, man!
Why don't you tell us everything
that you know, Reese?!
Like how Charlie's dead
'cause your dad didn't show up!
- I didn't know, Ryan.
- Stop fighting!
- He didn't tell me anything!
- Stop it!
- Come on!
- Stop, guys! That's enough!
Guys!
Look at that.
What?
Guys...
Look at the vent.
Air-conditioning duct.
It could go outside.
- Of course it goes somewhere.
- Ryan? Come on.
What, Reese? One of us
has to do something, all right?
- I'm not just gonna sit around.
- God, Ryan. Please.
What...
Hold this, Reese.
What?
All right.
- Reese, hold it!
- I got it.
Babe, relax.
What are you doing?
- What am I doing?!
- Yes, what are you do...
- I'm getting us outta here!
- Ryan.
- Hey, Charlie!
- Don't say that name, Ryan!
- Ryan! Please, man!
- Stop!
Don't say his name!
Don't say his name?!
- Charlie, Charlie, Charlie!
- Please.
Seriously,
this is not funny, okay?
- What was that?
- So sick of this!
- Stop! Stop!
- Ryan!
Come on, Charlie!
Show yourself!
Huh?!
Show me something, Charlie!
Come on!
- Shit!
- Ryan, please!
- Ryan.
- Stop it!
- Get down! Stop saying the name!
Do you not hear
what's going on?
Ryan, get down right now!
Goddamn it, Ryan!
Stop this!
You're being stupid!
You're gonna get yourself killed!
- Ryan, please, man!
- Stop it!
Okay. Now come down.
Will you just come down?
Please, stop it.
Reese!
I got this.
Aaah!
- Noooo!
- Ryan!
Noooooo!
Aaaah!
Cassidy!
Ryan, you're okay.
You're okay.
Talk to him!
- Ryan. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I gotta-
I'm gonna go
and I'm gonna get
something for you.
- I'm gonna go, okay?
- No! No, no, no!
I'm gonna go.
I'll be right back.
- Pfeifer? Pfeifer!
- No, don't! No, no, no!
Oh, my god, his leg!
- It's okay.
- It's broken! It's broken!
Reese!!
Oh, my god!
- Ryan!
- What happened?
- Cassidy!
- Take this. Take this.
Okay. Okay.
I got it. I got it!
- Ryan!
Ryan! Ryan!
Why did you leave?
I told you to stay!
Ryan!
Ryan! Ryan!
Ryan!!
- Ryan?
- Shh!
Ryan?
Ryan, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
He's okay.
Wait here.
Ryan?
Ryan.
It's okay. He's okay.
He's fine. He's all right.
Ryan.
- Ryan.
- Ryan, are you there?
Ryan.
No, no, no, no.
- Ryan!
- Where is he?
Oh, my god!
Reese, help her!
Cassidy!
Oh, my god!
Reese! Her neck!
It's worse!
Cass, come on.
Gotta go, gotta go, gotta go.
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Moments ago.
Ow! Ohh!
What are we gonna do, Ryan?
Wait, Cassidy.
- I don't know what
you want me to do.
- Cassidy!
I don't know
what you want me to do.
What do you want?
I don't know what to do.
Cassidy, do something!
Please.
- I can't do anything!
- Please!
- Aww! Please, Cassidy!
- I'm so sorry! I...
- Do something!
- I'm gonna get them.
No, no, no!
Don't leave!
Don't leave me here, Cassidy!
Please! Come back!
Holy shit.
Shit.
Cassidy?
Cassidy!
Guys!
Get outta the way!
Ryan!
Guys!
Guys, there's someone in here!
Reese! Help me, guys!
Guys, please come in here!
Help!
I'm sorry!
Please, don't!
Please!
Ryan?
Ryan.
Why?
Reese, why?
- Ryan.
- Oh, no, no, no.
Ryan!
Oh, my god.
Reese!
- Her neck! It's worse!
- Cass, come on.
- Okay, stay there.
- Reese, hurry! Hurry!
Gosh. What the hell?
Come on.
That's locked.
I can get up there.
POWER SAVE
Oh, no.
Please, no, no, no.
Please.
Shit.
I need a light.
Please work. Please work.
Please work.
Ryan's phone.
Yes! Yes.
Okay.
Reese, what's going on?
I don't know.
The light on the camera died.
You think it has something
to do with the show?
You guys...
You guys tried to stop it.
Pfeifer, please.
I think I found a way out.
- I need you to stay with Cassidy, okay?
- Okay.
Where the hell...
Dude, no.
No.
God.
Okay.
We're getting outta here.
It can't be.
No.
No, where is it?
It was right here.
It was just right here!
Where...
What the hell is going on?
Where are you?
Don't hang up.
Don't hang up!
Come on.
Oh, come on.
Please, please, please, please.
There!
Ugh! Come on.
Open!
No! No!
What?!
Come on!
- Come on!
- Reese!
Come on, don't hang up, dad.
Don't hang up. Pfeifer.
- Where's that coming from?
- It's my phone!
It's in the locker.
My dad's calling.
We gotta get it open!
Keep ringing.
Don't hang up.
Get outta the way.
Get outta the way!
Who is it?
Hello? Dad? Dad! Shh!
Dad! Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm at the school.
Dad.
He wants me.
He's coming for me.
No!
No!!
Why?!
Why?
Why did I do this stupid play?
I'm sorry
I asked you to do this.
Oh, Pfeifer.
Oh, god.
I'm sorry.
It's not...
Do you have your cell phone
on you?
Do you have your cell phone?
Check your cell phone.
See if you have service, okay?
God.
Cassidy!
- Oh, Cassidy!
- Where is she?!
Come on, Pfeifer, help me,
please!
Cassidy, come on!
The other battery's in.
I think we should...
Oh, my god.
Cassidy!
Wait, the fire alarm.
Come on, we gotta pull
the fire alarm.
What if he finds us?
Fire alarm.
There's one backstage.
Stay close behind me.
The fire alarm's right up here.
What if it doesn't work?
It's gonna work.
Okay, pull it.
Pfeifer, pull it.
He's gonna find us.
We have to try.
Reese.
Okay. Oh, my god.
It worked!
- We're getting out of here!
- It still worked!
We're okay.
Oh, Reese!
We're okay. We're okay.
We're okay.
We're getting out of here!
We're gonna be okay.
We're gonna make it.
We're all gonna make it.
We're gonna be fine.
We're gonna get out of here. The
firemen'll get here any second, okay?
Should we wait on stage?
No. No. No, we're gonna stay
right here, okay?
They're gonna find us
right here.
Oh, Reese.
What's that?
Do you not see it?
I don't see anything.
I saw a shadow!
I know I saw a shadow!
Pfeifer. Where?!
I don't see it.
Reese, I'm scared.
There's nothing there, okay?
There's nothing there.
You're okay.
All right?
- Oh, shit...
- Aaah!
Run! Go!
Up the ladder, go, go!
Run, run, run!
Go, go higher, go!
- Go, go!
- Come on!
Go! Go, go, go!
Oh, shit. Shit!
Keep climbing, keep climbing,
keep climbing!
Keep climbing, go!
No!
Reese!
Keep going!
- Take it, take it, here. Take it.
- Reese.
Shine the light.
Pfeifer, I need the light!
I know! I know!
Just close it!
- Come on!
- Give me the camera.
- Go!
- Shit! Shit!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Reese.
I don't wanna go any farther.
- Pfeifer, we can't stay here!
- I'm not going!
Come on.
We can't...
We can't stay here.
- Pfeifer, we gotta move.
- I don't know what's back there.
Pfeifer, listen to me.
You have got to move. Please.
Reese.
It stopped.
I think the police may be here.
- Okay, good.
- Someone's turned the alarm off.
- Good, let's just stay right here.
- No no no.
Please, they'll find us in here.
That means they're here.
The police are here.
We have to get downstairs.
We're gonna be okay.
- We just gotta get down, okay?
- I don't want to.
Okay. I'm right here.
I'm right here.
I don't want to.
They turned the alarm off.
The police are down there.
- Come on.
- I hate this.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
I'm right here.
I'm right behind.
Take my hand.
I'll get in front of you.
I'll go in front.
Okay?
Stay right here with me.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Okay.
Pfeifer, we gotta duck down
under the vents, okay?
Stay with me.
What?
What the hell?
Oh, no.
It's gonna be okay.
Watch your head.
Do you hear that?
Hear what?
What is that?
- Okay, it's no...
- Oh, my...
Oh, my god! Aaah!
Oh, my god!
Pfeifer, don't look.
Don't look!
Shh. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, guys.
This is all my fault.
Hey.
It's okay.
No. No.
Hey.
Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.
Okay?
Let's go.
- I got it.
- You got it?
Here, give it to me.
All right.
Where is everybody?
Where's the police?
Damn it, it's locked.
Why is it locked?
Where is everyone?
- It's open.
- Reese.
Where is everyone?
Why is no one here?
I don't see anybody.
There should be police here.
Okay.
We have to cross the stage.
Yeah, okay.
Let's go quickly.
Let's go.
We're gonna make it, pfeifer.
We got it.
Oh.
Okay. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes!
Oh! Oh!
We made it.
We made it!
Oh, we're okay.
Look, Pfeifer...
Pfeifer?
Help me!
I can't...
Pfeifer!
- Help!
- Shit!
Where are they?
Pfeifer?
Pfeifer!
Help!
Okay. What's wrong?
Okay. Okay. What's wrong?
- You gotta tell me what's wrong.
- I can't breathe.
What's wrong?
Come on.
What shall we do?
Don't worry.
He wants me.
He's coming-He's coming for me.
No one else.
Dost thou understand?
Thou shalt-
Thou shalt be safe here.
Art thou afraid?
I am no more.
Give me one last kiss.
It's okay.
He'll let you go.
Okay.
It's okay.
Pfeifer, you need to go, okay?
You're gonna be fine.
August, don't leave me.
- Hey, you don't have to do this.
- August, don't go, okay?
Pfeifer, you don't have to do that anymore.
You can go, all right?
August, for I am frightened.
Why are you saying that? Stop
calling me that. Would you go?
- August!
- Pfeifer, stop!
- Do not leave me!
- Pfeifer, stop calling me that!
- Please listen to me. You need to...
- August, please.
Pfeifer, goddamn you!
Why don't you leave?!
- Why aren't you leaving?!
- August, don't.
Goddamn it, Pfeifer, no!
No, no, no!
Pfeifer, please stop!
August, please don't leave me!
Please, don't go!
Stop! Please!
Pfeifer, don't let him do this!
- Please!
- August!
- Stop! Don't!
- No!
Don't let...
It's the police.
If anybody's here,
identify yourself.
Kitchen clear.
No sign of Pfeifer.
Pfeifer. Mrs. Ross.
It's the police.
What the hell?
Eh!
1 Paul 21.
1 Paul 81.
Suspects in the back room
to the right.
Lang, do you copy?
Charlie grimille?
You shouldn't say that name.
Lang.
Lang!
I need you back here.
Hold it there.
Lang!
No!
Subtitle edited by - Aorion -